(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-01T17:37:52.016372",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
rainbow in the sky
青い小鳥たち
blue little birds,
おいで歌おう 輪になり踊ろう
come on, let's sing and dance in a circle
in the evergreen trees
夢うつつで
lost in a dream,
恋する魔法にかかりかけられた
under the spell of love.
風にざさめく妖精 午後は おやすみ
Fairies whispering in the breeze, afternoon nap,
ユニコーンの背中で
on the back of a unicorn.
高いお城の塔から シャボン玉受け取ってね
From the tower of a high castle, catch the bubbles, okay?
王子さま！
Prince charming!
it's just a fairy tale
so it'll melt away like a lollipop
riding a flying whale
wondering when i'll wake up
お願い、ねえ、let me stay here...
Please, hey, let me stay here...
ring-a-ring o' roses, fa-la-la
round and round, fa-la-la-la
flying up and down, fa-la-la
i wanna stay here forever
ring-a-ring o' roses, fa-la-la
round and round, fa-la-la-la
flying up and down, fa-la-la
ここにきて
Come here,
時計の鐘
the clock strikes.
王子さまとはにかんでキス
Kissing shyly with the prince,
二人はいつまでだって
we could live happily
幸せに暮らすの
ever after.
but it was just my dream
the golden sunlight shows it's time to wake up
waiting quietly, shutting my eyes and i say
お願い、もっと、let me stay here...
please, more, let me stay here...
大地を踏みしめて 君は目覚めていく
Step firmly on the earth, you wake up and go
天使の微笑みで 連れ出して！
Toward that angel's smile, bring me out!
前進の微笑みで 連れ出して！
With a forward-facing smile, take me away!
孤独でも 一人じゃないさ
Even when alone, you're not by yourself,
生まれ出できたことに 必ず意味がある
There must be a reason why you were born.
優しさに 満ち溢れてる 青い星にありがとう
Overflowing with tenderness, thank you to this blue star.
You can smile again 太陽浴びて
You can smile again, bathing in sunshine,
You can fly away 世界は君の輝きを待っている
You can fly away, the world is waiting for your shine.
大空駆け抜けて
Run across the vast sky,
海原越えて行け
And cross the great ocean!
天使の投げキス 捕まえて！
Catch the angel's blown kiss!
大地を踏みしめて 君は目覚めていく
Step firmly on the earth, you wake up and go
天使の微笑みで 連れ出して！
Toward that angel's smile, bring me out!
前進の微笑みで 連れ出して！
With a forward-facing smile, take me away!
始まりはいつでも遅くないさ 何度でも立ち上がれ！
Starting is never too late, stand up no matter how many times!
最後まで あきらめないさ
Never giving up until the very end,
やり続けることに 必ず意味がある
There is always meaning in keeping on.
You just try again
闇を抜けて
Emerging from the darkness,
未来はいつも僕たちを待っている
The future is always waiting for us.
You just try again
闇を抜けて
Emerging from the darkness,
You just go away
未来はいつも僕たちを待っている
The future is always waiting for us.
大空駆け抜けて
Run across the vast sky,
海原越えて行け
And cross the great ocean!
天使の投げキス 捕まえて！
Catch the angel's blown kiss!
まだ誰も見たことない世界へ 飛び出そう明日
Jump out into a world no one has ever seen tomorrow!
振り返らない、と決めた
I decided not to turn around,
僕らを暖かく包む涙
The tears that warmly embrace us.
君が僕にくれた希望
The hope you gave to me,
大切に抱きしめて宙へ
Hold it close to your heart and head to the skies.
命は繋がれて行くから
Because life goes on, connected.
今はゆっくりお休み
Rest peacefully now.
君が望んだ未来を僕らの手で描いて行くよ 約束するよ
We'll paint the future you wished for with our own hands, I promise.
いつまでも どこまでも
Forever, no matter how far...
流れ落ちる涙
The tears falling down,
勇気に変えて行く
Turning into courage as we go.
天使の微笑みで 連れ出して
With an angel's smile, lead me away.
終わらない冒険に出かけよう
Let's set off on an endless adventure!
いつまでもどこまでも
Forever, no matter how far,
強くなれ、明日
Grow stronger, tomorrow!
大地をきみしめて
Stepping firmly on the ground,
きみは目覚めていく
You are awakening.
天使の微笑みで 連れ出して
With an angel's smile, lead me away.
始まりはいつでも遅くないさ
The beginning is never too late,
何度も 何度でも 何度でも 立ち上がれ
No matter how many times, get back up!
好きになって！もっと！私を見て！もっと！
Fall in love with me more! Look at me more!
恩返しは
My repayment is...
“愛のこもった投げキッスで”
"With a kiss full of love!"
気のせいじゃない 目は合ってるよ
It's not your imagination, our eyes are meeting!
ハート作って恋しちゃってください！
Make a heart and fall in love with me!
やれること何でもします NGなしで体当たり挑戦
I'll do anything, tackling everything head-on with no restrictions!
嫉妬、いやがらせには負けない
I won't lose to jealousy or harassment,
ふざけんな！実力で勝ってやる
Don't mess with me! I'll win with pure skill!
だからやめない負けず嫌い 私がいる (行くよ！)
That's why I won't quit, I'm a sore loser and I'm here! (Let's go!)
好きになって！もっと！私を見て！もっと！
Fall in love with me more! Look at me more!
恩返しは “愛のこもった投げキッスで”
My repayment is "With a kiss full of love!"
独り占めにする！もっと！夢を見せる！もっと！
I'll keep you all to myself! More! I'll show you dreams! More!
楽しんでって 愛のこもったスペシャルナイト
Enjoy this special night filled with love,
ファンサしちゃうぞ
I'll give you fan service!
お手紙も書いてください
Please write me letters too!
何度も読んで宝物にします
I'll read them over and over and treasure them.
スキャンダル まだ早いけど
Scandals are still too early,
裏切りません 宣言しときます
But I won't betray you, I declare that now!
知ったこっちゃない出世頭には負けない
I don't care about that, I won't lose to the rising stars,
ふざけんなよっちゅうことでやってやる
Don't mess with me, that's why I'll do it!
だからやめない負けず嫌い 私がいる (行くよ！)
That's why I won't quit, I'm a sore loser and I'm here! (Let's go!)
好きになって！もっと！私を見て！もっと！
Fall in love with me more! Look at me more!
恩返しは “愛のこもった胸キュンで”
My repayment is "With a heart-throbbing gesture of love!"
大完成！もっと！
A grand finale! More!
好きになって！もっと！
Fall in love! More!
私を見て！もっと！
Look at me! More!
恩返しは “愛の込め合った投げキスで”
"With a kiss packed full of love!"
気のせいじゃない 目は合ってるよ
It's not on purpose, our eyes meet!
ハート作って 恋しちゃってください！
Make a heart, fall in love please!
やれる こと 何でも します
I'll do whatever it takes!
ng 無し で 体当たり 挑戦
No NG's, all-out body-slam challenge!
エゴサ で 見つけ た アンチ の コメ
Spotted out of ego, an anti's comment!
ふざけん な ！ … 誰 より 分かって いる し
Just kidding... I understand better than anyone.
でも 大丈夫 ステージ に 立て ば みんな が いる
But it's fine, once on stage everyone is there!
(いくよ！)
(Here we go!)
好きになって！もっと！
Fall in love! More!
私を見て！もっと！
Look at me! More!
恩返しは “愛の込め合った投げキスで” (fooo！！)
"With a kiss packed full of love!" (Fooo!!)
夢に する ！ もっと ！ 夢 を 見せる ！ もっと
Let's make it a dream! More!
楽しんでって 愛 の こもっ た スペシャルナイト
Have fun, a special night full of love!
ファンサしちゃうぞ (^ω＜)
I'm gonna be your fan service! (^ω<)
お手紙も書いてください！
Please write me a letter too!
何度も読んで宝物にします
I'll read it over and over and treasure it!
スキャンダル まだ 早い けど
It's too early for a scandal!
裏切りません！宣言します (｀・ω・´)
I won't betray you! I declare it (`・ω・´)
嫉妬、嫌がらせには負けない
I won't lose to jealousy or teasing!
ふざけんな！実力で勝ってやる
No joking, I'll win with pure skill!
だから辞めない 負けず嫌い 私は いる
That's why I won't quit, I hate losing!
(いくよ！)
(Here we go!)
こぶし上げて！もっと！汗をかいて！もっと！
Raise your fist! More! Sweat it out! More!
恩返し は “ 愛 の こめっ た mona ビーム で ” ( fooo ！！ )
"With a mona-beam packed with love!" (Fooo!!)
大歓声！もっと！まだまだ！ねえ？もっと！
Loud cheers! More! Still not enough! Hey? More!
受け入れてね 愛のこもったわがままソング
Accept it, a selfish song full of love!
ファンサしちゃうぞ ( ・ω< )
I'm gonna be your fan service! (^ω<)
はぁ … 終わり が 近づく
Haah... the end is drawing near.
寂しいね
It's so lonely.
楽しいのに泣きそうだよ
I'm gonna cry even though I'm having fun!
次も次もまた会えるよね？
We can meet again and again, right?
(約束！)
(Promise!)
優しさに溢れている言葉も
Even words overflowing with kindness,
心ない誰かの言葉さえも
Even the words of someone heartless...
必要なんだ 必要なんだ
Are necessary, they're necessary!
強く なろう
I'll become stronger!
好きに叫べ！もっと！楽しんじゃえ！もっと！
Shout out your love! More! Enjoy it! More!
忘れないで特別になるように
Don't forget it, so it becomes a special day!
共に歌おうずっと！共に歩もうずっと！
Let's always sing together! Let's always walk together!
合言葉はとびっきりの l ・ o ・ v ・ e ( fooo ！！ )
Our watchword is a startling L-O-V-E! (Fooo!!)
好きになって！もっと！私を見て！もっと！
Fall in love! More! Look at me! More!
恩返しは “愛の込め合った投げキスで” (fooo！！)
"With a kiss packed full of love!" (Fooo!!)
夢に する ！ もっと ！ 夢 を 見せる ！ もっと
Let's make it a dream! More!
楽しんでって 愛 の こもっ た スペシャルナイト
Have fun, a special night full of love!
ファンサしちゃうぞ (^ω＜)
I'm gonna be your fan service! (^ω<)
突然降る夕立 ああ傘もないや嫌
Suddenly a passing evening shower,
空のご機嫌なんて知らない
I don't care about the sky's mood.
季節の変わり目の服は何着りゃいいんだろ
What clothes should I wear for the changing seasons?
春と秋どっかいっちゃったんだよ
Spring and autumn went missing somewhere.
息も出来ない 情報の圧力
I can't even breathe under the pressure of information.
めまいの螺旋だ 私はどこにいる
A maze of spirals, where am I?
こんなに こんなに 息の音がするのに
So much, so much, I can hear the sound of breathing,
変だね 世界の音がしない
How strange, I hear no sound from the world.
足りない 足りない 誰にも気付かれない
Not enough, not enough, nobody notices me,
殴り書きみたいな音出せない状態で叫んだよ
I screamed in a state where I couldn't make a punchy sound.
「ありのまま」なんて 誰に見せるんだ
"Just as I am" - who is that for?
馬鹿な私は歌うだけ
I'm just a fool singing away.
ぶちまけちゃおうか 星に
Let's smash it into the stars!
エリクサ\u200cーに張り替える作業もなんとなくなんだ
The work of restringing with elixirs is somehow nothing.
欠けた爪を少し触る
Gently touching the chipped nail,
半径300mmの体で必死に呟いている
Muttering desperately with a body of 300mm radius.
音楽にとち狂う ここが地球だな
Bump into music, this place is the Earth.
空気を掴んで 空を殴るよ
Grip the air and strike the sky!
なんにも起きない 私は無力さ
Nothing happens, I am powerless.
だけどさ その手で この鉄を弾いたら
But if I pluck this iron with that hand,
何かが変わって見えた…ような。
Something seemed to change... a little.
眩しい 眩しい そんなに光るなよ
Dazzling, dazzling, why shine so bright?
私のダサい影が より色濃くなってしまうだろ
My pathetic shadow just becomes darker and darker.
なんでこんな熱くなれちまったんだ 止まらない
Why have I become so fired up? It won't stop.
馬鹿な私は歌うだけ
I'm just a fool singing away.
うるさいんだって 心臓
"It's so noisy," says my heartbeat.
蒼い惑星 ひとりぼっち
A lone blue planet,
いっぱい音を聞いてきた
I've come hearing so much music.
回り続けて 幾億年
Revolving for billions of years,
一瞬だけでもいいから…ああ 聞いて 聴きよ
Even if just for a single moment... Oh, listen and hear me!
わたし わたし わたしはここにいる
I, I, I am here!
殴り書きみたいな音出せない状態で叫んだよ
I screamed in a state where I couldn't make a punchy sound.
なにかになりたい なりたい 何者でもいい
I want to become something, anything is fine, somebody!
馬鹿な私は歌うだけ
I'm just a fool singing away.
ぶちまけちゃおうか 星に
Let's smash it into the stars!
エリクサ\u200cーに切り替える作業となんとなくなんだ
Switching to the elevator, it feels a bit weird.
欠けた爪を少し触る
Gently touching the chipped nail,
半径300mmの体で必死に呟いている
Muttering desperately with a body of 300mm radius.
音楽にとち狂う ここが地球だな
Bump into music, this place is the Earth.
空気を掴んで 空を殴るよ
Grip the air and strike the sky!
なんにも起きない 私は無力さ
Nothing happens, I am powerless.
だけどさ その手で この鉄を弾いたら
But if I pluck this iron with that hand,
何かが変わって見えた…ような。
Something seemed to change... a little.
眩しい 眩しい そんなに光るなよ
Dazzling, dazzling, why shine so bright?
私のダサい影が より色濃くなってしまうだろ
My pathetic shadow just becomes darker and darker.
突然降る夕立 ああ傘もないや嫌
Suddenly a passing shower, ah, I don't even have an umbrella, how annoying
空のご機嫌なんか知らない
I don't care about the sky's mood
季節の変わり目の服は何着りゃいいんだろ
What clothes should I wear for the changing seasons?
春と秋どこいっちゃったんだよ
Where on earth did spring and autumn go?
息も出来ない 情報の圧力
Breathless, the pressure of information
めまいの螺旋だ わたしはどこにいる
A spiral of vertigo, where am I?
こんなに こんなに 息の音がするのに
Even though there are sounds of breathing, so much breathing
変だな 世界の音がしない
Strange, isn't it? There are no sounds of the world
足りない 足りない 誰にも気づかれない
Not enough, not enough, no one notices me
殴り書きみたいな音 出せない状態で叫んだよ
I screamed in a state where I couldn't even make scribbling-like sounds
「ありのまま」なんて 誰に見せるんだ
Who am I going to show "just the way I am" to?
馬鹿なわたしは歌うだけ
A foolish me just sings
ぶちまけちゃおうか 星に
Shall I spill it all out to the stars?
エリクサーに張り替える作業もなんとなくなんだ
Replacing strings with Elixir is also just a haphazard task
欠けた爪を少し触る
I touch my chipped fingernail slightly
半径300mmの体で 必死に鳴いている
With a body of 300mm radius, I'm desperately crying out
音楽にとつちゅう ここが地球だな
To music, this place is the Earth
空気を掴んで 空を殴るよ
Clenching the air, I punch the sky
窓を開けて 小さく呟いた
I opened the window and murmured softly
誰もしない 部屋で一人
Alone in an empty room
朝が来たよ 土砂降りの朝が
Morning has come, a pouring rainy morning
私のネジを 誰か巻いて
Someone, wind up my spring
昔のアニメにそんなのいたっけな
Was there anyone like that in old anime?
羨ましいな 皆に愛されて
I'm so envious, being loved by everyone
馬鹿な事言ってないで支度をしなくちゃ
Stop saying foolish things and get ready
涙の跡を隠す為
To hide the traces of my tears
もう口癖になった「まあいいか」
"Whatever" has already become my catchphrase
昨日の言葉がふと頭を過る
Yesterday's words suddenly crossed my mind
「もう君には 全然期待してないから」
"I'm not expecting anything from you anymore at all"
そりゃまあ私だって 自分に期待などしてないけれど
Well, of course, I don't expect anything of myself either
アレは一体どういうつもりですか
But what on earth do you mean by that?
喉元まで出かかった言葉
Words that came up to my throat
口をついて出たのは嘘
The lie that slipped out of my mouth
こうして今日も私は貴重な
And so today again, I live on
言葉を浪費して生きていく
Wasting precious words
何故隠してしまうのですか
Why do you hide it?
笑われるのが怖いのですか
Are you afraid of being laughed at?
誰にも会いたくないのですか
Do you not want to see anyone?
それ本当ですか
Is that really true?
曖昧という名の海に溺れて
Drowning in a sea called ambiguity
息も出来ないほど苦しいの
Suffering to the point where I can't even breathe
少し声が聞きたくなりました
I suddenly wanted to hear your voice
本当に弱いな
I'm really weak, aren't I?
一向に進まない支度の中途
In the middle of preparations that make no progress at all
朧気な頭で思う
Thinking with a hazy head
「もう理由を付けて 休んでしまおうかな」
"Shall I just make up an excuse and take a day off?"
いやいや分かってますって
No, no, I know, I know
何となく言ってみただけだよ
I was just saying it casually
分かってるから怒らないでよ
I know, so don't get angry
幸せだろうと 不幸だろうと
Whether happy or unhappy
平等に 残酷に 朝日は昇る
Equally and cruelly, the morning sun rises
生きているだけで精一杯の私に
For me, who is barely managing just to stay alive
これ以上何を望むというの
What more could you ask for?
何故気にしてしまうのですか
Why do you worry about it?
本当は愛されたいのですか
Do you actually want to be loved?
その手を離したのは誰ですか
Who was it that let go of that hand?
気が付いていますか
Are you aware of it?
人生にタイムカードがあるなら
If there were a time card for life
終わりの時間は何時なんだろう
I wonder what time the end would be
私が生きた分の給料は
Who is going to pay the salary
誰が払うんですか
For the time I've lived?
サンキュー ありがとうって言いたいの
Thank you, I want to say thank you
サンキュー ありがとうって言いたいよ
Thank you, I want to say thank you so much
サンキュー 一度だけでも良いから
Thank you, even if just once is enough
心の底から大泣きしながら
While crying my eyes out from the bottom of my heart
ありがとうって言いたいの
I want to say thank you
何故隠してしまうのですか
Why do you hide it?
本当は聞いて欲しいのですか
Do you actually want someone to listen?
絶対に笑ったりしないから 話してみませんか
I'll never laugh at you, so won't you talk to me?
口を開かなければ分からない
If you don't open your mouth, you won't understand
思っているだけでは伝わらない
Just thinking it won't convey anything
なんて面倒くさい生き物でしょう 人間というのは
What troublesome creatures we are, human beings are
ハロ ハロウェ
Hello, how are you?
あなたに ハロ ハロウェ
Hello, how are you to you?
ハロ 窓を開けて 小さく呟いた
Hello, I opened the window and whispered softly...
ハロウyu 誰がいない 部屋で一人
How are you? All alone in an empty room.
サンキュー ありがとうって言いたいの
Thank you, I want to say "thank you" from the bottom of my heart...
サンキュー ありがとうって言いたいよ
Thank you, I want to say "thank you" from the bottom of my heart.
サンキュー 一度だけでもいいから
Thank you, even if it's just once is fine.
心の底から泣きながらありがとうって言いたいの
From the bottom of my heart, crying, I want to say "thank you."
なぜ隠してしまうのですか
Why do I always hide it?
笑われるのが怖いのですか
Are you afraid of being laughed at?
誰にも会いたくないのですか
Do you not want to see anyone?
それ本当ですか
Is that really true?
曖昧という名の海に溺れて
Drowning in a sea called ambiguity,
息も出来ないほど苦しいの
It's so painful I can hardly breathe.
少し声が聞きたくなりました
I just wanted to hear your voice a little.
本当に弱いな
I really am so weak.
何故隠してしまうのですか
Why do I always hide it?
笑われるのが怖いのですか
Are you afraid of being laughed at?
誰にも会いたくないのですか
Do you not want to see anyone?
それ本当ですか
Is that really true?
あなたは今どこで何をしているですか?
Where are you now, and what are you doing?
この空の続く場所にいますか?
Are you in the place where this sky continues?
今まで私の心を埋めていたモノ
What filled my heart until now...
失って初めて気が付いた
I lost it, and only then did I realize.
こんなにも私を支えてくれていたこと
You supported me so much,
こんなにも笑顔をくれていたこと
You always gave me such a smile.
失ってしまった代償はとてつもなく大きすぎて
The price of losing it is too overwhelming,
取り戻そうと必死に手を伸ばしてもがいても
Even if I desperately reach out to take it back, struggling,
まるで風のようにすり抜けて届きそうで届かない
It slips through like the wind, almost reaching yet out of reach.
孤独と絶望に胸を締め付けられ逃げ
My chest is tightened with loneliness and despair,
心が壊れそうになるけれど
And my heart feels like it's about to break.
思い出に眠るあなたの笑顔が
Your smiling face living in my memories
私をいつも励ましてくれるの
Always encourages me.
もう一度あの頃に戻ろう
Let's go back to those days once more.
今度はきっと大丈夫
This time, it'll surely be okay.
いつも側で笑っていようねあなたのすぐ側で…
Let's smile together, right by your side...
あなたは今どこで何をしているですか?
Where are you now, and what are you doing?
この空の続く場所にいますか?
Are you in the place where this sky continues?
いつものように笑顔でいてくれますか?
Can you still smile just like always?
今はただそれを願い続ける。
Now, I will just keep wishing for that.
もう一度あの頃に戻ろう
Let's go back to those days once more.
今度はきっと大丈夫
This time, it'll surely be okay.
いつもの側で笑っていようよあなたのすぐ側で
Let's smile together, right by your side...
あなたは今どこで何をしているですか?
Where are you now, and what are you doing?
この空の続く場所にいますか?
Are you in the place where this sky continues?
いつものように笑顔でいてくれますか?
Can you still smile just like always?
今はただそれを願い続ける
Now, I will just keep wishing for that.
もうあなたから愛されることも
I will no longer be loved
必要とされることもない
or needed by you,
そして私はこうして一人ぼっちで
and now I'm all alone like this.
あの時あなたは何と言ったの?
What did you say at that time?
届かない言葉は宙を舞う
Words that can't reach dance through the air.
わかっているのに今日もしてしまう
Even though I know, I do it again today,
叶わぬ願いごとを
a wish that will never come true.
離さないで ぎゅっと手を握っていて
Don't let go, hold my hand tightly,
あなたと二人 続くと言って
saying it will last, just the two of us.
繋いだその手は温かくて 優しかった
The hand we held was warm and kind.
あなたはいつもそうやって私を 怒らせて最後に泣かすんだけど
You were always like that, making me angry and crying in the end,
後になって ごめんねっていうその顔
but afterwards, that face saying "sorry"—
好きだった
I loved it.
離さないで ぎゅっと
Don't let go, hold me tight,
そう想いきった あなたの腕の中にいたい
I want to be in your arms with all my heart.
二人で おでこをあわせながら
With our foreheads leaning against each other,
眠るの
we fall asleep.
もう二度とは会えないってことを知ってたの?
Did you know we would never meet again?
離さないで ぎゅっと あなたが好き
Don't let go, hold me tight, I love you.
もう一度だって笑ってくれないの?
Can't you smile for me one more time?
あなたの温もりが消えちまう前に
Before your warmth completely fades away,
抱きしめて
hold me tight.
もう二度とは会えないってことを知ってたの?
Did you know we would never meet again?
離さないで ぎゅっと あなたが好き
Don't let go, hold me tight, I love you.
もう一度だって笑ってくれないの?
Can't you smile for me one more time?
あなたの温もりが消えちまう前に
Before your warmth completely fades away,
抱きしめて
hold me tight.
もうあなたから愛されることも
I will no longer be loved
必要とされることもない
or needed by you,
そして私はこうして一人ぼっちで
and now I'm all alone like this.
あの時あなたは何と言ったの?
What did you say at that time?
届かない言葉は宙を舞う
Words that can't reach dance through the air.
わかっているのに今日もしてしまう
Even though I know, I do it again today,
叶わぬ願いごとを
a wish that will never come true.
離さないで ぎゅっと手を握っていて
Don't let go, hold my hand tightly,
あなたと二人 続くと言って
saying it will last, just the two of us.
繋いだその手は温かくて 優しかった
The hand we held was warm and kind.
あなたはいつもそうやって私を 怒らせて最後に泣かすんだけど
You were always like that, making me angry and crying in the end,
後になって ごめんねっていうその顔
but afterwards, that face saying "sorry"—
好きだった
I loved it.
離さないで ぎゅっと
Don't let go, hold me tight,
そう想いきった あなたの腕の中にいたい
I want to be in your arms with all my heart.
二人で おでこをあわせながら
With our foreheads leaning against each other,
眠るの
we fall asleep.
もう二度とは会えないってことを知ってたの?
Did you know we would never meet again?
離さないで ぎゅっと あなたが好き
Don't let go, hold me tight, I love you.
もう一度だって笑ってくれないの?
Can't you smile for me one more time?
あなたの温もりが消えちまう前に 抱きしめて
Before your warmth completely fades away, hold me tight.
忘れられてしまったことだけを覚えている
All I remember is what was forgotten,
ぽかりと空いた穴の先で君と出会った
I met you beyond the hollow void.
人生の終わりに
At the end of life,
何と思うかな
what will you think?
後悔か愛か
Regrets, love,
それとも覚めない夢か
or an unending dream?
まだ見ぬ明日に何を願うかな
What do you wish for in tomorrow you haven't seen?
確かな理想をほら描いてよ
Look, paint a clear ideal.
本当のことなんて悲しいだけだけど
The truth is only sad, but
嘘をつく方がもっと辛いでしょ
telling lies is even harder, isn't it?
正解を問う度息を詰まらせた
Every time I asked for the right answer, I held my breath.
追い付けないまま足は止まっていた
Unable to catch up, my feet had stopped.
昨日より今日より
Rather than yesterday, or today,
明日を選んだのなら
if you chose tomorrow,
どうかあなたの世界の絵に
please, onto the picture of your world,
そっとわたしの色を乗せて
gently add my colors.
今日も数え切れない夢に
Even today, in countless dreams,
ちょっと足が躅む
my feet tremble a bit.
願うのなら望むのなら
If you wish, if you desire,
共に夜明けを描きましょう
let's draw the dawn together.
たとえこれが
Even if this
映し出された幻でも
is a projected illusion,
確かに感じる
I surely feel
今あなたがそこにいること
that you are right there now.
名前も今日も
Names and today,
分からない君
you, whom I don't know,
さよならしてしまえば終わりだ
once we say goodbye, it's over.
君が居なきゃ穴は大きくなる
If you aren't here, the hole grows larger,
構わないさすぐ見付ける
but I don't mind, I'll find you soon.
世界 愛のどこかにいる君はどこ
Where are you in this world of love?
今生きているよ ここにいるよ
I'm living right now, I'm right here.
私...
I...
あたりは一面真っ直ぐな世界
All around is a straight world,
真っ直ぐ其方に落ちていく
falling straight towards you.
夢だからこの世界には忘れられぬ劇場の
Even so, if you desire,
それでも君が求めるなら
falling into this world's forgotten theater,
世界 愛のどこかにいる君はどこ
Where are you in this world of love?
今生きているよ ここにいるよ
I'm living right now, I'm right here.
名前のないまま...
Without a name...
Oh hi hoomans!
Hoomansのみなさん、この3年半、最後まで支えてくれて本当にありがとうね。
Hoomans, thank you so much for supporting me to the very end over the last three and a half years.
文章ではきっと、私の気持ちをすべて伝えきれないと思いますが、
Even in writing, I know I won't be able to fully convey my feelings,
本当にみなさんのおかげで、私の人生がとても豊かなものになりました。ここから離れていても、どんなことがあっても、みなさんのことを想っています。
You have truly changed my life for the better. Wherever I go, no matter what I face, I will remember you!
みなさんがくれた優しさと支えは、これからもずっと私の心の中にあります。おかげさまで、想像以上のことがたくさんできました。この気持ちは、一生忘れません。
I will always carry the kindness and support you showed me in my heart. I was able to do more than I ever imagined because of you. I will never forget this feeling!
私がhololiveにいたことが、誰かにとって少しでも力になれたなら、誰かに笑顔を届けられたら、生きていてよかったと心から思います。それは私にとって、かけがえのない宝物です。
I hope that my presence in hololive was a good one. Any moment of joy I might have brought someone makes me even happier to be alive!
一緒に過ごしてくれてありがとう。
Thank you for being here with me.
思いきりありのままの自分で楽しくいられるあたたい場所もくれてありがとう。
Thank you for giving me a warm space to be silly and have fun.
そしてNanashi Mumeiでいさせてくれて、本当にありがとう。
Thank you for letting me be Nanashi Mumei.
Nanashi Mumei